Contact

Email: nugentgreg28@gmail.com

Phone: +1 (315) 756-1160

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/greg- nugent-

91734921b

Top Skills

Solidity

React.js

Web3.js

Web Development

Full-Stack Development

Greg Nugent

Blockchain Architecture and DApp Development

New York

Summary

I am a topnotch blockchain and fullstack engineer. I have over 9 years of experience in software development. I am strong at Fintech, Blockchain, and Decentralized technologies.

I work with Solidity, Rust, Python, React.js, Vue.js, and Node.js in any types of projects.

Experience

Self-employed

Blockchain Software Developer

May 2021 - Present

- Design the infrastructure and architecture of ecosystems
- Develop smart contracts for and deploy on chains.
- Develop subgraph and Rest Apis
- Integrate smart contracts with React frontend.

React.js, Redux, Web3.js, Ethers.js, Uniswap, Chainlink, Solidity, Rust, Haskell

Citizen Finance

Lead Developer (Smart Contracts and Apis) January 2020 - March 2021

- Developed ERC20, ERC721 token contracts and deployed on BSC and Polygon
- Developed smart contracts for NFT marketplace, Staking Pool, Yield Farming
- Created subgraph, Rest Apis for token prices and user data.

Soldity, Openzeppelin, Chainlink, Truffle, Node.js, Web3.js, Polygon, Binance Smart Chain.

Coinomi

Full Stack Engineer September 2017 - December 2019

- Developed Mobile app interfaces for wallet
- Designed the architecture of the system and DB schema

React.js, Bitcoin, Web3.js, React Native, Ethereum

Upwork

Web Developer July 2016 - August 2017

- Developed Web apps for some clients
- Designed Microservices
- Developed REST Apis and Desktop apps

React.js, Django, ASP.NET, Laravel, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Node.js, Electron.js

Jitterbit

Software Engineer November 2013 - June 2016

PowerBI based websites

- Designed the architecture of the systems and developed microservices
- Designed a data conversion system and created a data visualization interface.
- Updated and optimized existing database and websites into React.js and $% \left(1\right) =\left(1\right) \left(1\right) \left$

React.js, Python, Tensorflow, Python libraries, C++, Microservices, PowerBI,

Education

University of Toronto

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (April 2008 - August 2013)

Vietnam National University

Finance and Financial Management Services · (June 2004 - September 2007)